Pedro Carmo

Résumé

Introduction

Hello, my name is Pedro Carmo. I'm a multidisciplinary designer based in foggy San Francisco, California.

Over the past 2 years, I've been a product designer at Teespring designing a new way for people shop and create custom products. Beyond Teespring, I also mentor design students at Designlab.

Before San Francisco, I was a product designer at Devmynd, rolling up my sleeves in the consultancy world in Chicago, Illinois. Apart from Devmynd, I also took part in building some amazing design communities at CreativeMornings Chicago and The Starter League.

Skills

Design, primarily focused on product thinking, interaction design, visual design, user experience, research and copywriting. Development, effecient in Html, Css & Scss architecture, Git SCM, Prototyping in Framer.js and working in Rails-dev environments.

Contact

Email: pe@drocarmo.com

Twitter: @drocarmo

Experience

Currently

Teespring, Product Designer

August 2014—Present

DesignLab, Design Mentor

August 2015—Present

Previously

Devmynd Software, Product Designer

November 2013—August 2014

Codal Inc., Designer & FE Engineer

March 2013—November 2013

Codal Inc., Design Intern

January 2013—March 2013

Futura IO, Design Intern

November 2013—August 2014

Freelance, Designer & FE Engineer

June 2012—October 2013

Education

The Starter League, Visual Design Student

Winter 2012 class

The Starter League, Advanced FE Development Student

Spring 2013 class